fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
Curse Sealing!
Out of character.
It appears he's quite tired...
To think you've become able to
handle Sealing Jutsu...
You've grown, eh, Kakashi...?
You...
Long time no see, Kakashi-kun.
Orochimaru...
A touch-and-go
Situation!!
Kakashi vs Orochimaru
Sorry, but...
I have no business with you, Kakashi-kun.
But I do with the kid behind you.
Why are you after Sasuke...?!
It's good for you.
You already got it, right?
You didn't have it before, did you...?
That.
That...
left eye Sharingan!
I want it, too...
The Uchiha power.
Come on. Get up.
W-What?!
B-Bugs?
They burst through the skin...
from inside his body?!
What a creepy guy!
Heh! What kind of bluff
are you trying to pull?
These things are called Parasitic Insects.
They attack their pray in groups
and eat Chakra...
If attacking in this amount...
you're finished, no mistake.
If you don't like that, give up.
That would be in your best interests.
If you use your left arm
technique on me,
I'll simultaneously have the bugs exploit
the opening from behind.
Conversely, if you use
your technique on the bugs,
I'll simultaneously exploit the opening...
Either way, you won't be able
to get through this.
An ace in the hole is something
you set aside.
Hey! Hold it!
You little thief!
Someone! Grab him!
Damn it!
Man, what a pigheaded kid.
Making us go to trouble!
You have potential, boy.
I liked your eyes earlier...
If you come with me,
you can become strong.
Follow me.
If you come with me,
you can become strong.
You can become strong.
Fight for me. If you do that...
I'll make you stronger.
Now, please live up to my expectations...
No longer...
will I...
It seems like you're proud
of your arms. You!
S-Stop it!
Stop!
No longer...
can I make things
blow up in my face!
Don't... underestimate me!
An ace in the hole is something
you set aside, right?!
you set aside, right?
What?! He could already
use his right arm?!
So the first half of the battle was
a strategic move
to make us think he couldn't
use his right arm.
Not bad... Zaku.
What's your purpose?
The recently built Sound Village.
That's my village, you see...
You already understand, don't you...?
Humph! Ridiculous ambition.
Oh, my... you said it.
But, for that I need various pieces
who will obey my every whim.
Take this!
So Sasuke is one of those pieces?
No. Sasuke-kun is an exceptional piece.
And the ones who are taking
the exams now...
are mere throw-away pieces.
My arms!
What's this?!
Earlier when I recommended
that you give up...
as a precautionary measure,
I gave a suggestion to the bugs...
to block that troublesome wind hole
with their bodies and remain still.
This is what a real ace in the hole is.
Punk!
Don't... come any closer... to Sasuke!
Even if you're one of
the legendary Sannin,
at the least,
I can kill you as you kill me!
What's funny?
What you say and what you do,
are all off.
What?
There's no point at all in
attempting such a seal.
You understand, don't you?
The heart to seek out
in pursuit of the goal,
no matter what obstructive power
there may be...
He is the possessor of that quality.
He's an avenger...
So you took advantage of that, eh?
However, Sasuke is...
At some point,
he will definitely seek me out...
in search of power.
Oh, and, you're going to kill me...?
Why don't you try?
That is, if you can...
Kill you as you kill me...?!
Am I an idiot...?
It seems... it's over.
The winner! Aburame Shino!
W-What is he, Neji?!
Byakugan!
He's something else...!
I can understand him calling bugs
with a Summoning Jutsu...
but he harbors bugs all over his body.
S-Say what?!
He's of the bug tamer race that
is passed down in the Leaf Village.
Speaking of which,
I've heard of it...
The story of a race that as
they come into this world,
possess the secret technique of loaning
their bodies to bugs
as a nest and fight using these bugs.
They fully control the bugs and
entrust most of the battle to the bugs...
I hear that they contract to keep
giving the bugs their own Chakra
as food for compensation.
So he's... the successor?
That was unfortunate, Zaku.
Why'd that happen to Zaku's arms?
Probably, that guy called
Shino or whatever...
exploited the opening and
stuck those bugs
into the exhaust opening in Zaku's hands.
If he were to fire the Slicing Sonic Wave
in that condition,
the energy with no way out
would expand in search of an exit...
His arms that are
gun barrels blow up...
and become useless.
Our relationship was only that
of having been given the same mission...
but... I'll even the score for you.
Whew. He gives me a chill, indeed...
What?! What?!
So Shino, you were that strong,
weren't you?! Damn it!
I thought he was
a creepy person from long before, but...
Oh...
S-Shino-kun, good... work...
Hey, you did it!
Yes... I'm counting on you guys, too.
He comes back like he's
the team leader or something! Damn it!
Umm, now then, I would like to
get right to the next match.
Kakashi-sensei!
Yo!
Not, "Yo!" Kakashi-sensei!
What about Sasuke-kun? Is he okay?
Well, he's fine.
He's sleeping soundly in the infirmary.
However, with ANBU Ops
standing as guards...
Oh.
Tsurugi Misumi
Kankuro
It's finally my turn.
Kankuro, he's totally underestimating this...
Humph. Idiot...
It's him...!
Unlike Yoroi, I don't get
careless with kids at all.
I'll say this first, once I do my technique...
give up no matter what...
I'll bring it to an end swiftly.
If so, I'll also...
bring it to an end swiftly!
Now then, please begin...
the third battle!
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
I believed in your words the whole time.
I wanted to be like you.
I thought it would be nice
if that happened.
So Ino, I want to fight the full-tilt you.
I'm no longer like I was before.
There's no point if I don't
exceed the serious you.
Next episode:
"Rivals Clash! The Hearts of the Girls are in Serious Mode."
Let's have a fair fight.